question_data = [
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Amazon acquired Twitch in August 2014 for $970 million dollars.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "DragonForce&#039;s &#039;Through the Fire and Flames&#039; is widely considered to be the hardest song in the Guitar Hero series.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; takes place on Shadow Moses Island.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Metal Gear Solid V: The Phantom Pain runs on the Fox Engine.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In the video game &quot;Transistor&quot;, &quot;Red&quot; is the name of the main character.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Resident Evil 4 was originally meant to be a Nintendo GameCube exclusive.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The ADAM collecters in the Bioshock series are known as Little Sisters.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The Fiat Multipla is a drivable car in &quot;Forza Horizon 3&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The game Garry&#039;s Mod originally took assets and codes from the popular Half Life 2 mod JBmod.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Minecraft wasn&rsquo;t the original name to Minecraft.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]

